In the concrete canyons where the landl
ord is king,
With a felt-tip pen making the "C" for
"colored" sing.
Refusing the rent to the dark-skinned
crew,
A ninety-seventy-five decree for the
red, white, and blue.
Then a full-page polemic for the Central
Park Five,
Wishing for the rope while they’re
barely alive.
Exonerated boys, but the man stays the
same,
Still defending the stance, still fan
ning the flame.
He's a medicine man for the "Birther"
disease,
Claiming Kenya's the home on the trop
ical breeze.
To the mash-un-TUCK-it PEE-kwaht, he
says with a sneer,
"You don't look like Indians" in a
revealing on air smear.
Then he rides down the gold-plated escal
ator slide,
Calling neighbors "rapists" on a xenopho
bic ride.
With "drugs" and with "crime" in a ra
cialized brew,
A hardline sermon for the chosen few.
Oh, John Pory was the first with the Af
rican pen,
And Woodrow Wilson segregated the fed
eral men.
Andrew Jackson's trail was a path made
of tears,
But a new ghost rises from the eugenics
years.
Joseph Arthur duh goh-bin-OH's hierarchy
of old,
Is dusted off now in a story oppulently
told.
Scientific Racism in a gilded new-age
suit,
With a Truth Social bird and a bitter,
dark fruit.
Deeper than the scholars in the eugenics
books,
It's all in the tweets and the "D E I"
hooks.
Catchier than a jingle, colder than the
ICE,
In the Golden Age of the weighted racial
ized dice.
Stephen Miller in the basement with the
vee-DAR-uh feed,
Sowing Camp of the Saints like a nation
alist seed.
Leaked emails flowing like a poisonous
wine,
Drawing a hard, eugenics-era line.
Paraphrasing Hitler's laws with a policy
grin,
Where the "Great Replacement" is the
original sin.
Fast forward to twenty-twenty-six, the
latest display,
The Obamas as primates in a jungle-theme
d fray.
"The Lion Sleeps Tonight" while the face
s are blurred,
A blatant trope from the seventy-nine
-year-old's word.
The white hous excuse, "Lion King," it's
just a meme, see?,
Before they blame an aide for the bigot
ry.
No apology offered, no regret in Leav
itt's burning crossed eyes
Just the "shithole" rhetoric and the
"garbage" of lies.
It's a legacy of provocation, sets of hy
sterical scenes,
In the land of the brave and the... qu
ote... "very fine" means.
Rivaling duh goh-bin-OH in the scientif
ic dark,
Leaving a "poh-kuh-HAHN-tuhs" and a
"shithole" mark.
Meme-worthy madness in a 2 A M trance,
While the G O P leaders do their usual
silence dance.
"Go back" to your countries, the Cong
ress-women hear,
A dog whistle blowing in the national
ear.
From the ninety-seventy rentals to the
jungle-themed post,
He's the anti-King host with the most of
the racist ghost.
Salute the flag, boys, but ignore the
sheets,
Only the "fine people" are marching on
the Truth Social streets.